(Penny:)Hey, you guys ready to order?
Uh, sure.
Okay, Priya?
(Priya:)Uh, I'll have
the shepherd's pie.
(Priya:)You want to split
that with me?
(Leonard:)Oh, no, no, no,
he doesn't.
(Priya:)Why not?
(Leonard:)Well, you have milk in
the taters,
(Leonard:)milk in the gravy,
parmesan crust.
(Leonard:)Your lactose-intolerant
boyfriend will turn
(Leonard:)into a gas-filled
Macy's Day balloon.
(Sheldon:)Not quite accurate. The Macy's
balloons are filled with helium,
(Sheldon:)whereas Leonard produces copious
amounts of methane.
(Leonard:)So, no, on the shepherd's pie.
Can we move on?
Yeah, a little tip:
he says he can eat frozen yogurt.
Do not believe it.
Sea bass!
I'll have the sea bass!
(Howard:)You gotta like this,
(Howard:)the girlfriend and the
ex-girlfriend bonding
(Howard:)over your rooty-tooty
stinky booty.
(Leonard:)Kill me.
It wouldn't help.
The human body is capable
(Sheldon:)of being flatulent for hours
after death.